翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Understanding this slide, and in particular these golden rules, is going to be critically important to you
理解这张幻灯片，特别是黄金法则，对你们来说相当重要
not just for project one or all the data structures you build in this class or even in the exams but also in your life.
不仅对这门课很重要，考试的项目、所有数据结构都会有所体现
而且会影响以后的生活
This is just the kind of thing that people expect programmers to know second nature.
这是期待程序员了解的第二天性
So to test your understanding so far--
为了测试你们的理解
and maybe you don't have it quite perfect yet--
也许你还没有完全吃透
I have the following problem for you to consider.
我有以下问题需要你思考
What I'd like you to do is look at this code and determine which of these four statements is true.
看一下这段代码，选出正确的描述
Now ideally what you'll do is you're with some other people right now.
理想情况下，此时所有人在一起
You will first work alone on the problem, come up with an answer, then you'll argue with each other,
你们先单独思考出一个答案，然后互相争辩
and then you'll watch me give away the answer and debate what that means.
最后讨论我给出的答案
So let's try that first step.
试试第一步
And if you don't have anybody else around, that's fine.
如果你身边没有其他人也没关系
But really try and work on this problem by yourself without looking at the answer.
尝试独立思考问题，而不是看答案
So pause the video and I'll wait here patiently.
请暂停视频，我会在这里耐心等待
So now that you've come up with your own personal theory, try and debate with others.
现在你应该有了自己的理论，跟其他人争辩一下吧
And pause.
暂停视频
And now finally, what I'm going to do is I'm going to show you the answer.
最后我要给出答案
So let's consider the Java Visualizer.
我们用一下 Java visualizer
This is just the result of clicking this link.
这只是点击链接的结果
So when I run this code, first thing that happens, a walrus gets built. I'll kind of skip that part.
运行代码时，首先构建一只海象，我会跳过这部分
So after this walrus is created and this integer variable is set up, we call doStuff.
创建了这只海象并设置了整型变量后，调用 doStuff
So doStuff, when it is called--
doStuff 被调用时...
well when we pass a parameter-- that means that this function is going to have its own scope.
我们传递一个参数，这意味着函数有它自己的作用域
It's going to have a variable called walrus and another called int and we're going to copy the bits.
它有一个 Walrus 类型的变量和另一个 int 类型的变量，我们将复制这些位
So if you understand what copying the bits means, that means I get a box called w, another called x.
你明白复制位意味着什么，意味着我得到了一个叫做 W 的盒子和一个叫做 x 的盒子
This is 64 bits.
这是64位
This is 32 bits.
这是32位
These 32 bits correspond with the number 9 get copied in
这32位被复制进来的是数字9
and these 64 bits, corresponding to the address that new shouted out after it finished its job,
而这64位是 new 完成任务后报告的地址
will be copied to w.
地址被复制到 W
So in other words, we have the same address sitting inside of these two boxes, which we represent in our visual metaphor using an arrow.
换句话说，两个盒子里有相同的地址，视觉上用箭头表示
So they're pointing at the same walrus.
它们指的是同一只海象
So in doStuff, we take this walrus
所以在 doStuff 中操作这只海象
and we subtract its weight
我们减去它的重量
and that is going to affect the walrus that [INAUDIBLE]..
这将影响海象
Next up, we're going to say x equals x minus 5,
接下来 x = x - 5
and the scoping rules for Java are just like any other language that you might have learned in the past-- say, Python.
Java 作用域规则与你过去可能学过的任何其他语言一样，比方说 Python
So we're going to be referring to the doStuff's version of x.
我们将引用 doStuff 中的 x
Now this is a 32-bit representation of the number 9
这是数字9的32位表示
and not the address of the number 9.
而不是数字9的地址
That's a very subtle but incredibly important distinction.
这是一个非常微小但极其重要的区别
It's the number, not the address of the number.
这是数字，而不是数字的地址
And so what that means is if I say x equals x minus 5,
这意味着如果执行 x = x - 5
we're actually just changing this number here
实际上只是在更改这个数字
and it's not causing an effect to backwash its way into the main function's scope.
而不会对 main 函数的作用域产生作用
So when the code finishes running,
代码结束运行时
then, we have a walrus pointing at--
我们有一只海象指向...
we'll have the walrus variable pointing at a walrus that did lose weight but x is unchanged.
海象变量指针确实减轻了海象的体重，但 x 保持不变
So hopefully that made sense,
希望你理解了
and if it didn't, make sure that you click on this link and make sure that you can follow all the steps
如果没有，可以点击链接执行所有操作
and maybe go back and re-watch one of the earlier pieces.
或许可以回去重新看一遍以前的视频
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）